

Chukwuekem Favour .O.

Software Engineer

Experienced Software Developer and Blockchain Enthusiast, constantly working towards building new and advanced generation software. I have worked at multiple levels of the quality assurance phase of professional software development, including Dapps, Centralized Fintech and Games. I am enthusiastic about innovation and I have a resilient attitude towards work.

feirie001@gmail.com

twitter.com/FavzyO Enugu, Nigeria, Enugu, Nigeria

+2347063292042

linkedin.com/in/chukwuekem-favour github.com/FeirieO

01/2016 - 11/2018, Enugu Ugarsoft Blockchain is a software company that focuses on building Blockchain solutions. Some their notable products are: Crypto Barons,

WORK EXPERIENCE

BackEnd Developer

Xend Finance

CareHive Project

02/2020 - 02/2021, Enugu, Nigeria Xend Finance is a defi platform for credit unions and cooperatives Achievements/Tasks

Worked on writing tests, performing code reviews and integrating third party services on the smart contract

Backend Engineer / Vfx Artist Quiva Games

07/2019 - 02/2021, Enugu Quiva Games is a Computer and Video Game publisher, With a major focus of integrating Crypto currencies and Blockchain assets into modern day genre of games.

SKILLS

Node js / C# / ASP.net /Web3 / Reactjs

ACHIEVEMENTS

Africa Comicade Gamathon Winner (08/2020) Led a team of developers to the top spot in the Africa Comicade Gamathon, with a game which was built under 48 hours

EDUCATION

Bsc. Economics
University Of Nigeria